# Lucky Fauzi

Indonesia, Bandung | 0895632035020 | Luckyfauzi2004@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT**

I am an ambitious person in terms of technology, especially in IT or Software Engineering. And I can be a dependable partner in a team or in individual because I have the best experience in software engineering as Front End Developer and Mobile Developer. I have goals to be a Fullstack Engineer so until now I still more learning about something new or materials about Fullstack engineer.

## **Work Experience**

### - QA (Quality Assurance)

Pt, Nusantara Technology, Jakarta (Remote)

Nov 2021 - May 2022

Participate to help being a QA on a website called Nusa LMS. Nusa LMS is an education website for learning about technology and can be accessed globally.

### - Teaching Assistant (Nusa Development Program)

Pt, Nusantara Technology, Jakarta (Remote)

Nov 2022 – Des 2023

Monitoring students who participate with the NDP program as A Teaching Assistance, for instance teach students who need additional class and assess students assignments.

### - Front End Developer

Pt, Nusantara Technology, Jakarta (Remote)

Feb 2022 - May 2024

Participate to help being a Front end developer in many project at local or international level included:

### • NDP (Nusa Development Program)

Feb 2022 - May 2022

NDP (Nusa Development Program) is a website company for providing information about education. And helping any participant to upgrade skills in programming.

### • Beyond Run

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Beyond run is a website for virtual and offline running events. Using Next Js and Typescript to develop the website.

#### LDX

May 2023 – July 2023

LDX is a Project website from Japan for importing and exporting a product globally. Participate to be a testing using React Testing Library

### Baton Handover System

Aug 2023 - May 2024

Is a website product for handling resignee to resign from the company and will be recap and made as a PDF report. Using Next js, Typescript and tailwind to develop the website.

• JCM (Joint Creaditing Mechanism)

Nov 2023 - Feb 2023

Is a website company for sharing information about cooperation between Indonesia and Japan. JCM is an initiative of the Government of Japan that encourages Japanese private organizations to invest in low-carbon development activities in Indonesia through incentives.

### - Mobile Developer

Pt, Nusantara Technology, Jakarta (Remote) Feb 2024 - May 2024

Fastrent

Feb 2024 - May 2024

Fastrent project from singapore is an application mobile for global rent of general items. Participate using React native to develop the app.

### Education

- SMK, Yadika Soreang – Software Engineer major 2020 – 2023

### **SKILLS**

**Programming:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Node js, Mysql, React Js, Next Js, Flutter, Tailwind Css, Scss, Graphql, React Native, React Testing Library, Jest, Github, Gitlab.

Software: Visual Studio Code, Figma, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Illustrator

Design: UI/UX, Logo Design